[Music]
Good morning morning morning to all of you
tonight Thank you very much
for the enthusiasm
[Music]
Welcome to b r Pacific Place
Jakarta and Welcome to the
fwd banking Kick Off 2025 sell to
success event with tline fwd OCBC stronger
together
we welcome the chief bank assurance officer
fbd insurance
ibuwi We want to navigate 2025
together with OCBC with the strength of FD
insurance in infrastructure technology
providing convenience for OCBC customers
in having insurance products
[Applause]
darpduran who will be
dis as the President Director of mwd
insurance my hope for 2025
is that the cooperation that has been built
over the past 4 months can be
improved to be even better to
achieve even higher results in
2025 and then I say
thank you very much once again for the presence
of all of you enjoy the event
enjoy
u Premier banking
Div ibu we
invite I think for 2025 We believe
we already have a strong foundation the
main reason also we finally
welcome new partners fwd as a
trusted partner
for isp because  What was conveyed earlier was
that Mrs. Des said that FWD
prioritizes customers, so its vision and
mission are the same as CVC NISP's. So
let's hold fast to
our vision and mission. I'm sure that in the future we
can go far together.
[Music]
This is the collaboration ceremony
between FWD Insurance and OCBC. It starts
in 3 2s. Host.
[Music]
[Applause]
Applause. UNT and everyone on this
extraordinary occasion.
[Music]
FD than